I just I just found the coolest thing
out so I I asked chat GPT how can I find
all the files that are pointing to a
hardlink file and a lot of you don't
know what hard links are and there's
people who question their Val their
validity I was actually making a thing
where I'm making a multic call binary
like busy box and Alpine if you don't
know what that is do a different search
and find out or come join me but you can
see over here there's number 333 right
that means there's three files pointing
to the same there's three different
iodes separate iodes pointing to the
same space on disk right and I was like
how do you do this and then I found lo
and behold the command find same file as
multi call oh did I do it
right what is going
on there we go and you can start that
search from the route so if you have
hard links to something and you have no
idea where they are on the file system
you could crawl your whole file system
and see which ones have the same file
the end